fitsmallbusiness.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy

The limited information captured about your visits to the website using log files is anonymous demographic information not specific to you (for example, internet protocol (IP) address; browser name; zip code; and access time). This information is used by Fitsmallbusiness.com to maintain quality of its service and to generate general statistics regarding the use of the site. This information may also be used to provide aggregate information to our advertisers, such as how many people saw their advertisement in a given timeframe, or how many clicked on it.

We collect personally identifiable information (“PII”) about you such as name, email, address, financial history in order to provide you with the services you have requested. Fitsmallbusiness.com does not, without your permission, rent, exchange, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information collected on our site except as described on this privacy policy. Personal information you provide to Fitsmallbusiness.com is used to service and process your requests, or connect you with a service which based on your request you may have an interest. To service your requests or connect you with services that may have an interest, third parties such as lead aggregators, financial advisers, insurance agents, banks- depending on your request — need to be involved. When you submit your personal information to us you may be contacted by these third parties regarding the services you have requested. Fitsmallbusiness.com cannot be, and is not, responsible for the privacy statements of websites outside of Fitsmallbusiness.com. Also, Fitsmallbusiness.com has no control over how information submitted by you to third party sites is collected and disseminated. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you link to from this site, so you can understand how these websites collect, store, and use your information, Fitsmallbusiness.com uses the services of other companies to perform various functions (e.g. statistical analysis, host web server, marketing, etc.). These service providers may not use your PII for their own promotional purposes.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and/or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us. As is true of most websites, Fitsmallbusiness.com also gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer our site, to track users’ movements around our site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Each time you make a request on our site, a cookie is sent back to our website from your computer. The cookie helps us (i) identify you (ii) personalize your experience on our site; (iii) dynamically generate advertising and content on web pages and in our newsletter, and target certain advertisements to your browser; (iv) determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements; (v) statistically monitor how many people are using our website, (vi) understand how many people open our emails; (vii) for what purposes these actions are being taken; (viii) as session timers; and (ix) generally facilitate your navigation. For these purposes our cookies are tied to your PII.

Your browser is generally set to accept cookies; however, you may set it up so it will not. This action may affect your experience on our site as you may not be able access some areas of the website or use some of the features on the site. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies that website has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers” below.  
This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Fitsmallbusiness.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party advertisers.

The ads appearing on our website are delivered to users by a reputable third-party ad server who is our agent for ad delivery and reporting. We do not share website usage information about users with this third-party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site. This third-party ad server uses cookies on this site, which allow it to recognize a user’s cookie when a user visits this site. The information that it collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable. We partner with third parties to provide users with lead aggregators, insurance agents, financial advisers, banks on our site. When a consumer requests any of these services, we will share their name, email address, phone number, and specific location, as necessary, to these third parties so that they may provide the requested service(s).

When a user comes to our site and requests a quote from our service providers, the user’s PII is then sent to a limited list of service providers that will be able to assist the user with his/her needs. The maximum number of companies this information will be sent to is 8. However, the number of companies could be lower depending on how many providers we have available in the state, county, or city that such services have been requested. PII will be sent with the utmost possible speed upon consumer submission of such information. Fitsmallbusiness.com will keep a copy of all consumers’ PII on its data base for the purposes of record keeping and any necessary provision of assistance to consumers or service providers. Once a consumer’s information is received by the service provider, response time is at the complete discretion of the service provider. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us by emailing info@Fitsmallbusiness.com. We make every effort to respond within 1 business week.

Fitsmallbusiness.com

The limited information captured about your visits to the website using log files is anonymous demographic information not specific to you (for example, internet protocol (IP) address; browser name; zip code; and access time). This information is used by Fitsmallbusiness.com to maintain quality of its service and to generate general statistics regarding the use of the site. This information may also be used to provide aggregate information to our advertisers, such as how many people saw their advertisement in a given timeframe, or how many clicked on it.

We collect personally identifiable information (“PII”) about you such as name, email, address, and city you are moving from in order to provide you with the services you have requested. Fitsmallbusiness.com does not, without your permission, rent, exchange, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information collected on our site except as described on this privacy policy. Personal information you provide to Fitsmallbusiness.com is used to service and process your requests. To service your requests, third parties such as lead aggregators, financial advisers, insurance agents, banks- depending on your request — need to be involved. When you submit your personal information to us you may be contacted by these third parties regarding the services you have requested. Fitsmallbusiness.com cannot be, and is not, responsible for the privacy statements of websites outside of Fitsmallbusiness.com. Also, Fitsmallbusiness.com has no control over how information submitted by you to third party sites is collected and disseminated. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you link to from this site, so you can understand how these websites collect, store, and use your information, Fitsmallbusiness.com uses the services of other companies to perform various functions (e.g. statistical analysis, host web server, marketing, etc.). Only information that is required to perform their specific function is provided, and it remains the property of Fitsmallbusiness.com. These service providers may not use your PII for their own promotional purposes.

Fitsmallbusiness.com has partnerships with financial sites, media sites and other service providers. Our co-branding program allows us to collect PII from these partner sites and provide the user with quotes for the requested service(s). The page(s) where this information is collected is managed and powered by Fitsmallbusiness.com however it has the look and feel of the partner site. In order to provide to you the services you request on our site, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. We use third-party services to verify your address, when your address is key to providing you with the services your request.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and/or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us. As is true of most websites, Fitsmallbusiness.com also gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer our site, to track users’ movements around our site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Each time you make a request on our site, a cookie is sent back to our website from your computer. The cookie helps us (i) identify you (ii) personalize your experience on our site; (iii) dynamically generate advertising and content on web pages and in our newsletter, and target certain advertisements to your browser; (iv) determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements; (v) statistically monitor how many people are using our website, (vi) understand how many people open our emails; (vii) for what purposes these actions are being taken; (viii) as session timers; and (ix) generally facilitate your navigation. For these purposes our cookies are tied to your PII.

Your browser is generally set to accept cookies; however, you may set it up so it will not. This action may affect your experience on our site as you may not be able access some areas of the website or use some of the features on the site. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies that website has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers” below.  
This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Fitsmallbusiness.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party advertisers.

The ads appearing on our website are delivered to users by a reputable third-party ad server who is our agent for ad delivery and reporting. We do not share website usage information about users with this third-party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site. This third-party ad server uses cookies on this site, which allow it to recognize a user’s cookie when a user visits this site. The information that it collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable. We partner with third parties to provide users with lead aggregators, insurance agents, financial advisers, banks on our site. When a consumer requests any of these services, we will share their name, email address, phone number, and specific location, as necessary, to these third parties so that they may provide the requested service(s).

When a user comes to our site and requests a quote from our service providers, the user’s PII is then sent to a limited list of service providers that will be able to assist the user with his/her needs. The maximum number of companies this information will be sent to is 8. However, the number of companies could be lower depending on how many providers we have available in the state, county, or city that such services have been requested. PII will be sent with the utmost possible speed upon consumer submission of such information. Fitsmallbusiness.com will keep a copy of all consumers’ PII on its data base for the purposes of record keeping and any necessary provision of assistance to consumers or service providers. Once a consumer’s information is received by the service provider, response time is at the complete discretion of the service provider. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us by emailing info@Fitsmallbusiness.com. We make every effort to respond within 1 business week.

Fitsmallbusiness.com  
dwaring@Fitsmallbusiness.com  
355 Lexington Ave, 18th Floor  
New York, NY 10017
